NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services, Maria Neira Files. 6174/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Somos El Futuro 20th Annual Legislative Conference, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  04/27-30/07. Preliminary agenda; Awards Luncheon Program; NYSUT Guide to Special Education brochures in English and Spanish; AFT brochures, Pathways to Success, in English and Spanish; NYSUT flyer in English and Spanish
- Race To The Top (RTTT), 2009 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Race to the Top Program Executive Summary, U.S. Department of Education, November 2009; full funding guidelines for publication in the Federal Register; Race to the Top Program Preamble and Major Changes; Race to the Top Application for Initial Funding
- RTTT, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  10/15/09. NYSUT Comments Regarding the Report on Improving the Preparation, Recruitment, and Retention of Urban Educators
- Race to the Top, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  8/19/09. Education Initiatives agenda; draft, Education Initiatives: Next Steps for NYSUT; presentation bullet points
- RTTT Applications: TN, DE, LA, MA and FL, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Comparative narratives
- RTTT: Weingarten AFT News Release, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Statement by Randi Weingarten, president, American Federation of Teachers, on "Race to the Top" Grant Awards, March 29, 2010; note about New York losing RTTT grant, NYSUT position
- NYS AFL-CIO Annual Labor Celebration, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  12/18/08 at Sheraton NY Hotel. Invitation to NYS AFL-CIO Annual Labor Celebration
- NYS AFL-CIO Annual Labor Celebration, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  12/17/09 at 6:00-9:00PM at Sheraton NY Hotel. Letter inviting NYSUT vice president Maria Neira; invitation to gala
- AFL-CIO Workforce Development Institute, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  01/28/09. Facilitative memo
- NYS AFL-CIO Conflict of Interest Policy, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Policy document, with cover letter; signed statement by Maria Neira, agreeing to policy
- NYS AFL-CIO: NYC Airport (Delta Airlines), 2010 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Letter to Maria Neira, describing anti-union efforts by Delta Airlines; open letter to Delta CEO from Neira, "An Appeal for Fairness at Delta Airlines"
- Task Force on Creating Pathways for New York's Youth, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Meeting agenda, May 24, 1991; outline of issues; notes for NYSUT president Tom Hobart
- Career Pathways Subcommittee Meetings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Agenda, June 26, 1991; list of subcommittee assignments; reports from advisory councils from other states; report, New York State Job Training: Workforce Preparation Evaluation Program Plan; testimony by National Alliance of Business before the House Ways and Means Committee re "Education and Human Resource Factors Affecting U.S. International Competitiveness," June 5, 1991
- Career Pathways Meeting [folder 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Wednesday, August 28 at 11:00AM in Syracuse Regional Office. Memo re meeting; U.S. Department of Labor Secretary's Commission on Achieving Necessary Skills report, "What Work Requires of Schools: A SCANS Report for America 2000," June 1991; brochure version; executive summary of U.S. General Accounting Office report
- Career Pathways Meeting [folder 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Wednesday, August 28 at 11:00AM at Syracuse Regional Office. Agenda for meeting of Standards and Inclusion Subcommittee, June 26; plans from Virginia and Wisconsin for improving workforce preparation
- Characteristics of Ideal Learning Environments (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Document
- Youth Apprenticeship, American Style: A Strategy for Expanding School and Career Opportunities, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  December 7, 1990. Report of a conference by Consortium on Youth Apprenticeship
- New York State Job Training Partnership Council, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Publication, "A Statement of Policy on Youth Employment Investments in New York State"
- The ASVAB Workbook - Exploring Careers, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Exploring Careers: The ASVAB (Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery) Workbook
- National Center on Education and the Economy - America's Choice: High Skills or Low Wages!, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  The Report of The Commission on the Skills of the American Workforce
- Education and Human Services Consortium - Structuring Interagency Partnerships to Connect Children and Families with Comprehensive Services, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Joint publication of the Education and Human Services Consortium
- U.S General Accounting Office - Training Strategies: Preparing Noncollege Youth for Employment in the U.S and Foreign Countries, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  May 1990. U.S. General Accounting Office Report to Congressional Requesters
- At Risk: A Nation and Its Youth-The National Youth Employment and Training Conference (Box 3, Folder 27)
  NYS Department of Labor (?) publication
- New York State Job Training Partnership Council-Creating a Vision: The Workforce Preparation System Of the Future, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Publication
- State Education Department-Education Statistics New York State, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  January 1991. Booklet prepared especially for members of the legislature
- New York State Job Training Partnership Council, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  NY State Education Department Basic and Expanded Basic Skills: Scales for Validation Study, July 1990; fact sheet from the White House, "America 2000: The President's Education Strategy," April 18, 1991; Statement of Senator Edward M. Kennedy at the Executive Session on S. 2, "The Strengthening Education for American Families Act"; Report to the Board of Regents on Career Preparation Validation Study; article, "Preparing a World-Class Work Force," Vocational Education Journal, May 1991; Pathways for New York State's Youth, showing charts for enrollment and graduation activity, 1985-89, comparison of percentage of public and private school graduates entering institutions of higher learning
- Career Pathways Task Force, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  October 31. Notice of meeting; Proposal by the Rochester School-to-Work Transition Initiative, October 28, 1991; Cornell University publication, "Creating Apprenticeship Opportunities for Youth: A Progress Report from the Youth Apprenticeship Demonstration Project in Broome County, NY," September 1991; brochure, "The University at Albany: A $4 Billion Engine for Economic Growth 1990-1999"; Statement of Senator Edward M. Kennedy at the Introduction of "The High Skills, Competitive Workforce Act of 1991," October 1; Cornell publication, "Adapting German Apprenticeship to New York State: Report on a Symposium Convened by S. H. Hamilton," June 7, 1990; Outline of Proposed Recommendations and Recommendation Options of the Task Force on Creating Career Pathways for New York's Youth; updates by subcommittees; related memos
- Task Force on Creating Career Pathways [folder 1 of 3], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Monday, October 7 at 10:30AM in Room 5-B, SED. Monthly Labor Review article, "Shared Training: Lessons from Germany," March 1991; draft task force reports
- Task Force on Creating Career Pathways [folder 2 of 3], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Monday, October 7 at 10:30AM in Room 5-B, SED. Meeting materials, including draft report, proposed recommendations, and cover letter
- Task Force on Creating Career Pathways [folder 3 of 3], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Monday, October 7 at 10:30AM in Room 5-B, SED. Proposed recommendations and options; other documents
- Administrative Committee, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  10/20/09 at 12 Noon in Auditorium. NYSUT document, "Managing a Harassment-Free and Respectful Workplace"; training program evaluation forms; memo calling meeting, noting training topic
- Administrative Committee, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  6/09/09 at 1:00PM. Agenda; presentation bullet points re Obama's Pre-K-Higher Education agenda; AFT presentation points, "The View from the States"; presentation, "Expanding the Promise of Education in America," White House Domestic Policy Council
- Administrative Committee, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  1/27/09 at 1:00PM. Memo
- Administrative Committee, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  9/24/08 at 10:00AM. Keynote Speech by NYSUT Vice President Maria Neira to the Capital Region Human Resources Association Diversity Gala, October 16, 2008; handwritten notes; training materials on trust and self-evaluation for integrity
- Administrative Committee, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  6/10/08 at 1PM in Auditorium. Agenda; AFT presentation bullet points, "From Members to Unionists: Connecting with NYSUT's Next Generation"
- Administrative Committee, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  3/11/08 at 1PM in Auditorium. Agenda; discussion group notes
- Administrative Committee Meeting, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  1/30/08 at 11PM in NYSUT Auditorium. Agenda; article from WorkingUSA: The Journal of Labor and Society, "A Strategic Choice Framework for Union Decision Making," March 2005; presentation bullet points, "Strategic Choice and Building Union Capacity"; handwritten notes
- Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  11/04/09 at 1PM in Conf. Rm B&C. Agenda; press releases: from Department of Labor, "Statement by U.S. Secretary Hilda L. Solis on reports detailing international child labor and forced labor," and from National Labor Committee, "Retail Giant Flouts Recommendation of Centers for Disease Control: Wal-Mart's Sick Leave Policy Risks Spreading Swine Flu," November 3, 2009; definition of NYSUT's Social Justice Agenda
- Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  3/18/09 at 1:00PM. Agenda; Report of Vice President Maria Neira
- Advisory Committee, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  10/14/08 at 1:30PM in Conf. Rm. B&C. Memo
- Advisory Committee, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  6/4/08 at 1PM in Conf. Rm A&B. Agenda; radio script by Shorr Johnson Magnus Strategic Media opposing proposed property tax cap; related communications plan; draft of letter to state legislators; Code of Ethics Frameworks for NYSUT Local Leaders, Benefit Fund Trustees and Their Employees Provided by NYSUT Member Benefits Trust; confidential memorandum from NYSUT general counsel James Sandner re ethics issues raised by association with Harris, Conway and Donovan, June 3, 2008; New York Times editorial re property tax cap; press release from National Education Association (NEA) recommending endorsement of Barack Obama for president, June 3, 2008; NYSUT Briefing Bulletin, "Summary of the Report of the Commission on Property Tax Relief," June 2008
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  12/04-05/09 at Headquarters. Draft discussion paper, "NYSUT's Principles for Leading Excellence in Higher Education"; consolidated financial statements, draft as of September 1, 2009; report of vice president Neira; report of general counsel; resolution in support of reconsideration of marriage equality bill; issues briefing papers; Report of the NYSUT High School Initiatives Task Force on Improving Graduation
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  09/25-26/09. Presentation for Board of Directors, "NYSUT Redistricting Background and Resolutions"; Representative Assembly materials (tentative program, deadlines); financial statements for NYSUT Building Corporation as of July 31, 2009; Report of the Executive Director; NYSUT Member Benefits Trust and Corporation Report; Conflict of Interest Policy for NYSUT Officials and Employees
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  7/23/09 at Saratoga Hilton Hotel. Agenda; minutes of Board of Directors meeting of April 1, 2009; minutes of Executive Committee meetings of June 4 and May 12, 2009; reports of officers; NYSUT Building Corporation financial statements as of May 31, 2009; Building Corporation membership meeting minutes of July 23, 2009; memo re proposed building purchase, July 23, 2009; requests for affiliation; presentation points re redistricting; NYSUYT Constitution and Bylaws, effective 2009-2010; Implementation of Actions by the 2009 NYSUT Representative Assembly, April 2-4, 2009
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  07/23/09 at 9AM in Saratoga Hilton. Report of vice president Maria Neira, focusing on the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act and the Race to the Top; biography of Regent Chancellor Merryl Tisch; handwritten notes; NSYUT presentation points, "Using the Power of LAP (local action project) to Improve/Enhance Achievement"
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  2/27-28/09. Update from State Education Department on the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009 (ARRA); report of vice president Neira
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  2/27/09-2/28/09. Agenda; minutes of meeting of December 12-13, 2008; minutes of Executive Committee meeting of January 15, 2009; legislative report; officers reports; publication, Educator's Voice, NYSUT's journal of best practices in education, spring 2009; NYSUT Building Corporation financial statements; related materials
- Workforce Development Institute Board of Directors Meeting, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  01/28/09. Agenda; employee manual (draft), effective April 1, 2008; executive director's report; program reports; status of contracts
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  12/12-13/08. Agenda; 2009 NYSUT Representative Assembly Committee Nominations, revised as of December 12, 2008; presentation of dues proposal; minutes of Executive Committee meeting of October 24, 2008; proposed amendments to NYSUT Constitution and bylaws; officers reports
- NYSUT Board of Directors Retreat Meeting, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  9/29/08 at 3PM in Kathleen's Office. Report of Committee to Review Responsibilities of Board Members; excerpt from NYSUT Policy Manual re Board of Directors
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  8/12-13/08. Agenda; 2008-09 NYSUT Budget; minutes of Executive Committee meeting of August 13, 2008; officers reports; NYSUT Endorsement Recommendations NYS Assembly, U.S. Congress; press releases opposing tax cap, cuts to higher ed
- New Board of Dir. Orientation, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  8/11/08 at 9AM at Headquarters. Agenda; presentation materials; 2005-2006 Local Leaders' Guide, by NYSUT Research and Educational Services; Information Bulletin; Briefing Bulletin re special education requirements, January 2008
- NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  August 2008. Minutes of Board of Directors meetings of April 9 and 12, 2008; minutes of Executive Committee meeting of June 5, 2008; Report of the Executive Director; other officers' reports; position papers by NYSUT committees; proposed 2008-2011 committee recommendations; Implementation of Actions by the 2008 NYSUT Representative Assembly; survey results compiled by Task Force on the Roles and Responsibilities of Board Members
- NYSUT Board of Directors, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  2/29/08 at 4PM in Auditorium. Agenda; officers' reports, including report of the general counsel; financial statements; minutes of Executive Committee meeting of February 29; materials re Community Service Award winners
- Committee Appointments, 2005-2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Committee nomination forms; memo to Board of Directors from NYSUT president Richard Iannuzzi re committee appointments
- NYSUT Board of Directors Mail Ballots, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Memos and ballots re bullying, suicides, and harassment statement, endorsement in Attorney General primary, endorsement of state senate candidate
- 08-09 Budget, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Printed NYSUT budget for Cabinet presentation, May 7, 2008; salary adjustment schedules for management/confidential compensation; narrative document, "Compensation for the President of NYSUT," recommending large increase; confidential memo re Research and Educational Services staffing budget, March 27, 2008; memo from director of finance and administration expressing concern re continuing large overages in charitable giving, lack of oversight
- Budget Meeting, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  April 12, 2006 at 3:30PM at Chuck's Office. Schedule for management/ confidential salary proposals, 2006; memo to officers re 2006-2007 NYSUT budget, April 5, 2006; list of Research and Educational Services staffing, dates of hire
- Cabinet Meeting, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  12/02/09 at 12 Noon. Meeting agenda
- Cabinet Meeting, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  10/21/09 at 12:30PM in Executive Conf. Rm 1. Meeting agenda; draft text for radio ad; draft outline for mid-year cuts campaign; handwritten notes
- Cabinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  09/09/09 at 12:30PM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Agenda; questionnaires for officers; NYSUT Education and Learning Trust Board of Trustees meeting agenda for September 9, minutes of April 15 and June 2 meetings, proposed budget, and related materials
- Cabinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  6/17/09 at 12:30PM. Agenda; materials re charter schools
- Cabinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  5/6/09 at 12:30PM. Cabinet meeting and Officers' meeting agendas; memo from director of finance and administration re CUNY Professional Staff Congress request for increased financial support; highlights of 2009 school nurse survey; list of charitable contributions of over $5,000 for the period September 1, 2008, to April 30, 2009
- Cabinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  04/15/09 at 11:30AM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Agenda; CSEA dues structure
- Cabinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  3/25/09 at 12:30PM. Agenda
- Cabinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  3/4/09 at 12:30PM. Agenda for Cabinet meeting; agenda for Representative Assembly; delegate bulletin for Representative Assembly; draft list of invited speakers
- Cabinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  1/6/09 at 12:30PM. Agenda; NYSUT talking points re governor's 2009-2010 budget; tentative Representative Assembly program; NYSUT Regents' Report Card
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  12/2/08 at 12:30PM. Agenda; memo re regional office responses to the economic crisis, December 3, 2008; NYSUT consolidated statements of operating expenses for the years ended August 31, 2008 and 2007; statement of financial position as of August 31, 2008; NYSUT membership comparison as of October 31, 2008 vs Fiscal Year end 2008, by regional office; handwritten notes
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  10/1/08 at 12:30PM. Agenda for Cabinet meeting; agenda for Board of Trustees meeting; status of regional office projects as of October 1, 2008; minutes of the Board of Trustees of the NYSUT Education and Learning Trust, March 18 and May 16; projected Education and Learning Trust budget; handwritten notes
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  9/11/08 at 11:00AM. Agenda; Executive Committee resolution re Establishment of the New York State United Teachers Nonqualified (Management/ Confidential) Employees' Retirement Plan, September 11, 2008; draft Leader Access proposal, re levels of secure access to NYSUT web site
- Cabinet Meeting, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  8/11/08 at 12:15PM in Video Conference Room. Facilitative memo
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  08/04/08 at 1PM in Executive Conf. Rm 1. Article from New York State School Boards Association newsletter, On Board, re testing; article in New York Sun re testing; handwritten notes
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  05/07/08 at 12PM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Agenda
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  April 1, 2008 at 11:30-1:00PM. Agenda; NYSUT Solidarity Fund application
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  03/18/08 at 10AM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Agenda for Cabinet meeting; agenda for NYSUT Education and Learning Trust Board of Trustees meeting, March 18; memo re check disbursement approvals; request for financial support for new Cornell ILR Extension course (denied)
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  2/26/08 at 12:30PM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Agenda; draft memo re liaisons to the Board of Regents
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  1/16/08 at 12:30PM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Agenda; resolutions submitted for consideration at the Representative Assembly
- Cabinet, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  1/3/08 at 12:30PM in Exec. Conf. Rm 1. Agenda; document by Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, The Problem with Property Tax Caps; map of election districts and school districts in NYS; preliminary draft, Amendment to the Rules of the Board of Regents and the Regulations of the Commissioner of Education re tenure
- CWA Bargaining Agreement: Contract, 2005-2008 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  NYSUT and Communication Workers of America Local 1141 Collective Bargaining Agreement, January 1, 2005-December 31, 2008; cover letter to NYSUT officers from NYSUT president Richard Ianuzzi
- Duty Descriptions for Titles Established Effective Jan 1, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Memo from NYSUT executive director Pauline Kinsella to CWA president and staff representative, referencing job duties for titles established by collective bargaining agreement, April 4, 2007
- Speaking Engagement ELT-SRP Summer Training Program, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  06/27/11 at 11:00AM in Desmond, Albany. Speech by NYSUT vice president Maria Neira; hand-notated draft; agenda for SRP (school-related personnel) training schedule
- ELT Meeting: Yankowski, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  02/25/08 at 4PM in Maria's Office. Facilitative correspondence
- ELT Budget Meeting, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  08/23/10 at 1PM in Maria's Office. Education and Learning Trust statement of financial activities
- ELT Meeting, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  06/08/10 at 11AM in Maria's Office. Survey results and analysis
- NYSUT ELT: Conflict of Interest Policy and Whistleblowers Policies, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  02/03/10. Ballots by Maria Neira approving resolutions re whistleblower and conflict of interest policies; description of policies
- NYSUT ELT Board of Trustees Meeting [folder 1 of 2], 2009 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  12/02/09 in NYSUT HQ. Agenda; minutes of meeting of Education and Learning Trust Board of Trustees of September 9, 2009; course descriptions
- NYSUT ELT Board of Trustees Meeting [folder 2 of 2], 2009 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  12/02/09 in NYSUT HQ. Course descriptions
- ELT: Fiscal Agent, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  09/17/09. Memo recommending that Education and Learning Trust be designated as the fiscal agent for the statewide Teacher Centers meetings to comply with new federal payment policy under the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (ARRA)
- ELT Minutes, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  09/09/09. Minutes of special meetings of the Board of Trustees of the NYSUT Education and Learning Trust, April 15 and June 2 (minutes approved 09/09/09)
- ELT Summer Training, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  07/20/09 at Gideon Putnam. Summer training agenda; Maria Neira talking points; presentation outline, NYSUT's Position on Reform; facilitative memos
- Proposed ELT Instructors, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  List of proposed instructors; cover memo
- ELT New Course Proposal Meeting (Immediately After R&E Managers Meeting), 2009 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  04/13/09. Board of Trustees meeting agenda; course outlines re cyber-bullying, cultural proficiency, autism spectrum disorders, other topics
- NYSUT ELT Report, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  09/08-01/09. Report; financial (activities) statement
- ELT Regional Coordinators Meeting, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  10/3/08 at 6PM in Hilton Garden Inn. Agenda for Regional Coordinators' meeting; regional reports for Utica/Rome, Capital District/northern New York, Southern Tier, Suffolk, NYC, Syracuse region, and western NY
- ELT Minutes, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  10/01/08. Minutes of Board of Trustees meeting
- ELT Budget, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  10/1/08. Agenda of Board of Trustees meeting; minutes of March 18 and May 26 meetings; projected budget for 2008-09
- ELT Regional Coordinators' Minutes, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Friday, October 3, 2008
- Mark of Excellence Award Video Taping, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  09/11/08 at 4PM in Cotton Hill Studio, Colonie, NY. Outline of questions re marketing campaign; facilitative memos